Guide to the James Paddock Collman Papers SC1138
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
James Paddock Collman papers
1960-1997
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Collman, James Paddock
SC1138
100 Linear Feet
Access to Collection
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Acquisition Information
Gift of James P. Collman, 2012-2016.
Chemistry.; Collman, James Paddock; Stanford University. Department of Chemistry
- Lab Notebooks
  - William Leonard, 1992 Summer; 1 volume(s) (Box 19)
  - William Leonard #2, 1992 Summer; 1 volume(s) (Box 19)
  - Dave Offord #1, 1 volume(s) (Box 19)
  - Dave Offord #2, 1 volume(s) (Box 19)
  - Farnham - good experiments, complete index, 1 volume(s) (Box 19)
- Course Materials
  - Chem 255, 1985 Winter (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Chem 255, 1984 Spring (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Chem 255 course notes, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Chem 255, 1983 Spring (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Chem 131 teaching evaluations, 1983 Winter (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - J.P. Collman - Chemistry 131, 1983 Winter (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Chem 131, 1983 Winter (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Chem 131, 1982 Winter (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Chem 255, 1990 Spring (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Chemistry 255, 1987 Spring (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Chemistry 151, 1991 Winter (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Chemistry 001, 1989 Spring (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Chem 33, 1990 Winter (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Future Chem 33 final question (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Chemistry 33 class notes, 1989 Winter (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Chem 33, 1982 Winter (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Chemistry 33, 1978-1979 Winter (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Chemistry 131 Course review, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Chem 131, 1984 Winter (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Chem 133, 1988 Winter (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Chemistry 131 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Chemistry 131, 1986-1987 Winter (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - [Chemistry] 131 course evaluations, 1986-1987 Winter (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Chem 131, 1987 Winter (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Chem 131. course evaluations., 1987 Autumn (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Chem 131, 1987 Fall (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Lecture notes (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - [Chemistry] 131. Course evaluations, 1984 Autumn (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Chem 131, 1984 Fall (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Chemistry 131, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Chem 131. Class notes, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Grants
  - Fuel cell correspondence (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Fuel cell patent (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - A study of oxygen electrode catalysts. Proposal submitted to ONR, LBL, AFOSR, EPRI. Not funded., 1982 May & 1982 Jun (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Studies of oxygen electrode catalysts. Submitted to DOE. Not funded., 1984 Jul 24 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Catalyst candidates for oxygen cathodes proposal. Submitted to AFOSR. Still pending., 1985 Jul 23 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Catalyst candidates for oxygen cathodes. proposals to AFOSR submitted 7/14/87 for 3/1/88-2/28/91. Not funded., 1987 Jul 14 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Competitive renewal proposal of fuel cell NSFCHE81-10545 Not funded (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Fuel cell drawings (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - CMR seed proposal: a search for naturally occurring superconductors (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - CMR seed grant: "A new class of metallo-..." year 3, 1985 May 1-1986 Apr 30 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - CMR seed grant: "A new class of metallo-organic..." year 2, 1984 Jul 1-1985 Apr 3 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - CMR proposal: "A new class of metallo-organic..." year 1, 1983 Jul 1-1984 Jun 30 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - ONR contract proposal, year 1, N00014-84-K-0403, 1984 Jul 1-1985 Jun 30 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - ONR contract "Liquid crystalline ... " N00014-84-K-0403 year 2, 1985 Jul 1-1986 Jun 30 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - ONR contract N00014-84-K-0403 year 3, 1986 Jul 1-1988 Jun 30 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - NSFCHE81-10545 Fuel Cell + 6 year 3, 1983 Jul 1-1984 Jun 30 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - NSFCHE-8110545 Fuel Cell year 2, 1982 Jul 1-1983 Jun 30 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - NSFCHE-8110545 Fuel Cell + 6 year 1, 1981 Oct 1-1986 Jun 30 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Fuel cell scientific text, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Fuel cell scientific text, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - ARPA - Synthesis of new types of catalysts materials. June 1, 1975-May 31, 1976. (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - ARPA proposal - Synthetic catalytic electrodes, 1974 Jun 1-1975 May 31 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - NSF - U.S.S.R. Exchange Program, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - NSF - Reversible Oxygen Electrodes, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - RANN Proposal, 1977 Sep 1-1980 Aug 31, 1977 May (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Fuel cell preproposal file (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Office for Interdisciplinary Research Relevant to Problems of Society NSF (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - NSF-RANN "Reversible Oxygen Electrode -- collaborative search ...", 1974 Dec (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - NSF renewal proposal -- Catalysis by Coordination Complexes, GP39451, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - NSF -- Catalysis by Coordination Complexes & Organometallic Compounds, 1973 May 1-1974 Jun 30 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - NATO no. 504 -- renewal, 1974 Apr (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - NATO grant, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - NIH - Catalysts for Oxidation of Toxic Gases, AP00794, 1969 Jun 1-1971 May 31 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - NIH - Catalysts for Oxidation of Toxic Gases, 2-FBJ-405 0 Proposal (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - NIH proposal: The Chemistry of Metal Chelates, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - NIH Research grant proposal. Reactions of Chelated Ligands of Biological Interest, 1961-1964 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - NSF grant, GP-7867 Addition Reactions of Planar d8 Complexes, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - NSF senior postdoctoral fellowship proposal, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Proposal to NSF for grant -- Additional reactions of Planar d8 complexes, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - NSF proposal for research grant -- Resolution & Coordination Isomerism of Metal Chelate ..., 1960 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - NSF research grant proposal -- Addition Reactions of Planar d8 Complexes, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - NSF proposal - Mechanistic Patterns in Homogenous Catalysis, 1968 Sep (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - NSF - Mechanistic Patterns in Homogeneous Catalysis, GP-9101 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - NF grant renewal application - "Mechanistic Patterns ...", 1969-1970 Sep (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - ACS-PRF Research grant proposal - Chemistry of Metal Chelate Rings, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - ACS-PRF unrestricted grant proposal - Nov. 20, 1967 PRF 3635-C3, 1967 Nov 20 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - J. P. Collman NIH Proposal (less pp 1-16, 65-69) P-450 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - DEFG03-86ER45245 DOE Cont. proposal, 1991 May 1-1992 Apr 30 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - DEFG03-86ER45245 Continuation year proposal, 1990 May 1-1991 Apr 30 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - A quest for a new superconducting...competing renewal DOE, 1989 Apr 1-1992 Mar 31 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - A quest for a new superconducting...submitted to ONR, AFOSR, NSF, DOE, AOR Funded by DOE, 1985 Jan (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - NIH Pharm. Sciences Program Highlight, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - NIH Equipment Grant Supplement Gas Chromatograph $16,205, 1991 Nov 1 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - NIH Competing renewal 5R01GM17880, year 18, 1988 Mar 1-1988 Nov 30 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - NIH (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - NIH Proposal (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - NIH Continuation year 19 5R01 GM17880, 1988 Dec 1-1989 Nov 30 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - NIH GM17880-17 Continuation year proposal - year 17, 1986 Dec 1-1988 Feb 29 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - NIHGM17880-16 Continuation proposal - year 16, 1985 Dec 1-1986 Nov 30 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - NIH Continuation application for NIHGM17880-15 - year 15, 1984 Dec 1-1985 Nov 30 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - NIHGM17880-14 Continuation proposal year 14, 1983 Dec 1-1984 Nov 30 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - NIH (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Figures for NIH Competing Renewal 5R01GM17880, 1988 Mar-1992 Nov (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - NIH5R01GM17880-12 Continuation Proposal yr 12, 1981 Dec 1-1982 Nov 30 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - NIH5R01GM17880-11 Continuation Proposal yr 11, 1981 Dec 1-1982 Nov 30 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - NIH5R01GM17880-10 Continuation Proposal yr 10, 1979 Dec 1-1980 Nov 30 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - NIH5R01GM17880-09 Continuation Proposal yr 09 Models for Cytochrome P-450 Hydroxylases, 1978 Dec 1-1979 Nov 30 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - NIH5R01GM17880-08 Models for Cytochrome P-450 Hydroxylases, NIH Competing Renewal proposal, 1977 Dec 1-1982 Nov 30 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - NIHGM17880-07 Continuation proposal Mixed Func. Oxygenase Models, 1976 Dec 1-1977 Nov 30 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - NIHGM17880-06 Continuation proposal Mixed Func. Oxygenase Models, 1975 Dec 1-1976 Nov 30 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - NIHGM17880-05 Competing Renewal Proposal, 1974 Dec 1-1977 Oct 31 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - NIHGM17880-04 Mixed Function Oxygenase Models yr 4 Cont prop, 1973 Dec 1-1974 Sep 30 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - NIHGM17880-03 Mixed Function Oxygenase Models yr 3 Cont prop, 1972 Oct 1-1973 Sep 30 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - NIHGM17880-02 Mixed Function Oxygenase Models yr 3 Cont prop, 1971 Oct 1-1972 Sep 30 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - NIHGM17880-01 Mixed Function Oxygenase Models prop, 1970 Oct 1-1974 Sep 30 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - NSF, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - NSF 8814949 Final Report, 1988 Dec-1992 May (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - NSF CHE88-14949 REY Supplement, 1990 Dec 1-1991 Nov 30 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Progress report NSFCHE88-14949, 1989 Dec 1-1990 Nov 30 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - NSF CHE8814949 Supplemental proposal synth. studies in homogenous catalysis, 1990 Dec 1-1991 Nov 30 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - NSF CHE-8814949, 1990 Dec 1-1991 Nov 30 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - NSF CHE83-18512 Creativity extension, 1987 Jan 1-1988 Dec 31 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - NSF CHE83-18512 Continuation proposal, 1986 Jan 1-1986 Dec 31 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - NSF CHE83-18512 Continuation proposal yr 2, 1985 Jan 1-1985 Dec 31 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - NSF CHE78-09443 Competitive renewal proposal, 1984 Jan 1-1986 Dec 31 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - NSF CHE78-09443 Continuation year (2nd) of 2 year extension, 1983 Jan 1-1983 Dec 31 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - NSF CHE78-09443 Proposal for 2 year extension, 1982 Jan 1-1983 Dec 31 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - NSFCHE78-09443 continuation proposal for 3rd year, 1981 Jan 1-1981 Dec 31 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - NSFCHE78-09443 continuation proposal for 2nd year, 1980 Jan 1-1980 Dec 31 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - NSFCHE78-09443, request for rebudgeting, correspondence (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - NSFCHE78-09443 proposal - begin 3 years continuation, 1979 Jan 1 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - NSF Grant MPS75-17018 and CHE75-17018 Synth Stud in Homo Catal and Orgmtlc Chm (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - NSF supplemental proposal for equip. Supplement to CHE75-17018. (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - An experimental quest for excitonic superconductivity Collman/Little to NSF, 1985 Oct 29 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - NSF Proposal: Synth Stud in Homo Catal and Orgmtllic Chem (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - NSF GP20273x and MPS70-1722 Ao3 Mech Pat in Homogenous Ctalysis (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Catalysis by Coordination Complexes and Organometallaic Compounds, 1973 Jun 1-1974 May 31 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - NSF (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - NSF Reu (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - NSF CHE-9015474 REU Site prop. w/Zare not funded, 1990 Jul-1992 Sep (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - X-ray Wavelength Modulation Spectro proposal, 1990 Mar 1-1991 Feb 28 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - CHE-8919687 (Solomon) supplemental for SQUID Magnetometer, 1990 Aug-1991 Jul (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Phase II Modernization Proposal, NSF (Departmental) (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - FT NMR Proposals (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Prop to NSF for Computational Facility Keith Hodgson (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - XAS Studies of Liquid Crystalline...SSRL prop w/Hodgson (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - CMR REU Proposal - Harville, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Prop to biomed rsch comm for nih small equip grant funds - spectrophometer (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - NATO 85/300 extension w/ Eric Rose, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Joint proposal to Binational Science Foundation in Israel with Milstein (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Renewal proposal for NATO 85/300...w/Rose (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - NATO Grant w/Rose 85/300 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - L'Her US-France Cooperative Grant (unfunded) (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - JPC/L'Her NATO Grant, 1981-1983 Mar (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - JPC/Meunier Collaborative Grant (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Collman/Milstein/Bau US-Israel Collaborative proposal (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Trips
  - VIII I.C.C.C. Vienna, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - XI I.C.C.C. Israel, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - XIII I.C.C.C. Poland, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Trip file Eastman-Kodak, 1970 Jun (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Gordon Conference on Electrochemistry, 1970 Jan (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - NSF Chemistry Advisory Panel meeting, Washington DC, 1972 Oct 12-14 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Research Corporation Panel meeting, Buck Hill Inn, Pa., 1972 Oct 10-11 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Eastman Kodak, 1972 Sep 20-22 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - XIV I.C.C.C. conference, Toronto, 1972 Jun 22-28 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - A.C.S. Summer Symposium, SUNY Buffalo, 1972 Jun 18-21 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Texas A & M, 1972 Sep 18-20 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Eastman Kodak, 1972 Jun 15-16 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - University of Canterbury, Christchurch, New Zealand, 1972 Mar 10-May 29 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Research Corporation, 1972 Feb 6-13 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - The University of Chicago, 1972 Feb 2 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Eastman-Kodak, 1972 Jan 18-20 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Lecture commitments, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - University of Minnesota, 1971 Nov 18 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - ACS Meeting, Washington DC. Correspondence, 1971 Fall (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Europe, 1971 Oct 9-27 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Arapahoe Chemicals, Research Corp., 1971 May 12-14, 1971 May 13-14 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - NSF Advisory Panel meeting, Los Angeles, 1971 Mar 27-28 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Santa Barbara, 1971 Mar 21-23 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Kodak, Cornell, 1971 Mar 16-17, 1971 Mar 18 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Research Corp. - Cottrell Advisory Committee meeting, Puerto Rico, 1971 Feb 14-22 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Arapahoe Chemicals, 1971 Jan 12 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - NSF Panel meeting; University of North Carolina, 1971 Oct 28-30, 1971 Oct 30-Nov 4 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Research Corporation, 1971 Oct 6-8 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Eastman Kodak and ACS meeting, Washington DC, 1971 Sep 8-14 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Eastman Kodak, 1971 Jun 3-4 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Ventron Corporation, 1972 Dec 15 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - MIT-Harvard, 1972 Dec 14-15 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Eastman Kodak, 1972 Dec 12-13 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Fourth Industrial Affiliates Workshop, 1972 Sep 11 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - University of Utah; Colorado State Univ., 1972 Oct 18. 1972 Oct 19 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - ACS Pacific Coast Conference, San Francisco, 1972 Oct 16-18 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Caltech; Cal State, Fullerton; UC Irvine, 1973 Nov 26-29 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - University of Southern California, 1973 Nov 9 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Industrial Affiliates Symposium, 1973 Nov 12-14 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Conference of the Robert A. Welch Foundation, Houston, 1973 Nov 5-7 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Oregon Graduate Center, Wednesday, 1973 Dec 12 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Oregon Graduate Center, 1973 Sep 6 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Northwestern University, 1973 Jul 24-28 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Univ. Wyoming; Procter & Gamble; Wayne State U.; UNC; Eastman Kodak, Lederle Labs., 1973 Sep 20-Oct 4 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Gordon Conference; International Conference, 1973 Aug 5-10, 1973 Aug 12-16 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Montana State; Allied Chemical; Eastman; Pfizer; Esso; Hoffmann-LaRoche., 1973 May 30-Jun 15 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - NSF Panel meeting, Dallas, Texas, 1973 Apr 7-8 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - U.S. Soviet Catalysis Program (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Eastman Kodak, Shell Development. ACS Southwest Regional meeting., 1974 Dec 8-12 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Iowa State University, DuPont, University of North Carolina, Univ. of Rochester, 1974 Nov 10-22 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - UCLA, 1974 Oct 10 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Oregon Graduate Center, 1974 Sep (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - ACS Meeting, Atlantic City, N.J., 1974 Sep 9-11 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Eastman Kodak; Penn. State Univ.; Univ. of Kansas, 1974 Sep 11-17 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Eastman Kodak and 15th conference on Reaction Mechanisms, CSU, 1974 Jun 23 - Jul 2 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - U.S.S.R., 1974 Jul 11-20 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - 15th Conference on Reaction Mechanisms, Ft. Collins, Colo., 1974 Jun 24-28 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Meeting of the French Chemical Society & visit to Univ. of Calabria, 1974 Jun (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - NATO Summer School, Corfu, Greece, 1974 Jun 8-16 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - U.S. - Japan Seminar -- Prospects in Organotransition Metal Chemistry, Hawaii, 1974 Apr 30-May 3 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Los Angeles ACS meeting, 1974 Apr 2-3 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Univ. of Illinois and Eastman Kodak, 1974 Mar 24-28 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Mid-Winter Solid State Research Conference, Irvine, 1974 Jan 8 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Eastman Kodak, Exxon, Hoffmann-LaRoche, Notre Dame, 1975 Oct 27-Nov 7 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Industrial Affiliates Lecture, 1975 Nov 13 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Oregon State University, 1975 Oct 13 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Searle Laboratories, Haverford College, 1975 Sep 29-Oct 3 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Bioorganic Chemistry and Enzyme Models, Honolulu, 1975 Aug 25-29 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Montana State University, 1975 Jul 21-16 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - National Organic Symposium, Ft. Collins, 1975 Jun 22-26 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Eastman Kodak and Xerox, 1975 Jun 9-12 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Utah State University, 1975 May 30 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Univ. of California, Santa Cruz, 1975 May 8 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - University of Nebraska, 1975 Apr 3-4 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - ACS National meeting, Philadelphia, 1975 Apr 6-11 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Annual Chemical Congress, York, England, 1975 Apr 7-11 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Kettering Research Foundation Scientific Advisory Committee meeting, 1975 Jan 27-28,30 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Bioinorganic Workshop, New Orleans, 1975 Jan 6-7 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - University of Chicago, 1976 Nov 22 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Eastman Kodak, 1976 Oct 25-27 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - University of Victoria, 1976 Oct 20-22 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - ACS - Univ. of Michigan, 1976 Sep 15-18 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - fall ACS meeting - San Francisco, 1976 Aug 29-Sep 3 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Gordon Conference, 1976 Aug 16-20 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Eastman Kodak Company, 1976 Jun 7-8 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Biological Aspects of Inorganic Chemistry, UBC, Vancouver, 1976 Jun (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Brigham Young University, 1977 Feb 22 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - University of Nebraska; Eastman Kodak, 1977 Feb 1-7 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Princeton, Univ. of Arizona, Kettering Foundation, ACS-Chicago section, 1977 Mar 13-26 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Eastman Kodak, 1978 Apr 3-4+ (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Gordon Research Conference, Santa Barbara, 1978 Jan 23-28 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Eastman Kodak Company, 1978 Jan 12-13 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - U.S. - U.S.S.R. Symposium, Kiev and Cambridge, England, 1976 Jul 1-15 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Rutgers Univ., Allied Chemical, Merck, and Bell Telephone, 1976 Apr 11-20 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Eastman Kodak Company, 1976 Mar 16-17 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Fuell Cell meeting, 1982 Nov (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Ohio State University, 1976 May 5-7 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Kettering Research Laboratory, 1976 Feb 9-11 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - University of Nebraska, 1976 Jan 26-28 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Gordon Conference, Santa Barbara, 1975 Dec 29 - 1976 Jan 2 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Cornell, 1977 fall (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Exxon, 1977 May (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Case Western Reserve, 1977 Dec 1 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Univ. of California - San Francisco, 1977 Nov 11 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - California Institute of Tech.; Univ. of Southern California, 1977 Nov 3-4 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - IUPAC Meeting, Tokyo, 1977 Sep 4-10 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Purdue, Union Carbide, Univ. of New Hampshire, Hoffmann-LaRoche, Exxon, Eastman, 1977 Oct 10-20 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Univ. of California - San Diego, 1977 Jun 8 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Biology Summer School, Seattle, 1977 Jul 8 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - U. C. Berkeley, 1977 May 13 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Eastman Kodak, 1977 Apr 27-29 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Fuel Cell meeting - CalTech, 1977 Apr 20 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Catalysis Workshop, Lyon, 1978 Nov 7-9 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - U.S. - Japan Workshop, 1978 Jun (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - U.C. Davis, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Monsanto Company, 1978 Oct 9-11 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Caltech, 1978 Oct 4 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Eastman Kodak and Grace Co., 1978 Oct 16-19 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Cambridge, England and Continent -- Sabbatical, 1978 Apr-Jul (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Fuel Cell meeting - Cal Tech, 1979 Dec 9-13 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Eastman Kodak, Rochester, 1979 No. 6-8 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Gordon Conf., 1979 Jul (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Terry Collins trip to visit Prof. T. Spiro at Princeton, 1979 Jun 26 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Hercules - Wilmington, Del. Eastman Kodak, 1979 Jun 24-27 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Workshop in Organometallic Chem. Pingree Park, Ft. Collins, Co., 1979 Jul 15-18 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Kodak. NAS meeting, Raleigh, 1979 Apr 17-26 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Univ. of Arizona, Tucson, 1979 Mar 24-25 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - New Zealand ANZAAS Conference, 1979 Jan 22-26 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - ACS Meeting, Hawaii. Nat'l Chem Congress of Pac Basin Soc, 1989 Dec 17-22 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Oregon - Bend research, 1989 Sep 7-12 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Minnesota, 1989 Aug 5-23 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Lecture tour of French-speaking Univ's in Switzerland, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Symposium on Electrocatalysis -- ECS meeting in LA, 1989 May 7-12 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Karcher Lecture, Univ. of Oklahoma, 1989 May 4 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Univ. South Carolina, 1989 Apr 27-28 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Symp. Ferromagnetic High Spin Based .... JPS Session Chair, 1989 Apr 9-12 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Am. Physical Society - St. Louis, 1989 Mar 20 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - NAS regional meeting, San Francisco, 1989 Feb 21 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - AAAS meeting, SF Hilton, 1989 Jan 16-17 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Schuitt Symposium in Catalysis and Surf. Sci. Univ. of Delaware, 1988 Oct 11 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - University of Dijon, 1988 Oct 3-10 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Multinuclear Magnetic Resonance [course] NATO Adv. Studies Institute. Robert Hembre., 1988 Aug 19-Sep 4 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Phil Hampton/Bob Hembre to attend ACS mtg. in LA, 1988 Sep 25-30 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Univ. of Oregon lecture, 1988 Sep 20-25 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Minnesota, 1988 Aug 3-17 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - University of Nebraska-Lincoln, 1988 May 7 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Univ. of Nevada-Reno, 1988 May (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - NAS - Louisville - UNC trip, 1988 Apr 23-May 1 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Frontiers in Chemical Research lecture, Texas A&M, 1988 Apr 10-15 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Chem. Div., REU Panel, NAS bldg. Washington D.C., 1988 Feb 8-9 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Natl. Advisory General Medical Sciences Council, NIH (Bethesda), 1988 Jan 27-29 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Los Alamos, 1987 Sep 16-22 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - 12th Int. Symp. on Macrocyclic Chem. Hiroshima, Japan, 1987 Aug 20-23 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Seminar at Berkeley, 1987 spring (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - International Workshop on Novel Mech of Supercon, Berkeley, 1987 Jun 22-26 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Seminar at Univ. Chicago, 1987 May 11 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Univ. Illinois - Nelson J. Leonard Lecture, 1987 Mar 24-27 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Denver ACS meeting, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Case Western Reserve Frontiers in Chemistry Lecture, 1987 Mar 19 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Senior Center PA Distinguished Lecture 2-3 pm [Palo Alto], 1987 Feb 9 (Box 4, Folder 68)